ANTON SHAPOSHNIKOV

UI Developer (React.js)

Remote or hybrid office Based in Ennis, Ireland (possible relocation inside Ireland) I am developer with 3 years commercial experiense in web development. I am considering Front-End developer possition with a lot of focus on UI developing. Every day I delve deeper into the study of React, JavaScript and TypeScript technologies.

I am team player, but also I can work independently and make decisions in my area of responsibility. My goal is to constantly evolve professionally, day of day.

77

INFO

CONTACT

+353 (85) 202 2738 shaposhnikov.web@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO

http://shaposhnikov.in/

LINKEDIN

https://linkedin.com/in/shaposhnikov-dev/

GITHUB

http://github.com/purr-purr

SKILLS

React.js

TypeScript

JavaScript (ES6+ / JQuery)

Next.js

Chakra UI

Redux

HTML5 (JSX)

CSS3 (SASS / SCSS / PostCSS)

Animated HTML5 Banners

Page SEO Optimization

Ant-design / Bootstrap / MUI

Gulp / WebPack

NPM / Yarn

Git / GitHub

Photoshop / Figma

Mobile First CSS

BEM / SUIT

i18next

Page Speed Optimization

LANGUAGES

English - A2 (Pre-Intermediate)

Ukrainian - Fluent

Russian - Native

PROJECTS

A few of my latest projects that i've been involved in:

- · WHIH Charity Fund: https://whih.com.ua/
- DeHive App: https://app.dehive.finance/
- Rad Live: https://app.rad.live/

You can find more of my projects on my website: https://shaposhnikov.in/

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER (REACT.JS)

Blaize Tech (Blockchain) 09.2021 - 09.2022 (1 year)

Implemented features:

- · Implementation UI using mobile-first CSS and SUIT approach.
- Implementation UI using Ant-Design library and Chakra UI library with using CSS in JS approach.
- · Creating projects on Next.js to run SPA, based on React.js
- · UI Scaling and project component encapsulation.
- Support and implemented new features for projects.

UI DEVELOPER (JS)

Delivery Group (E-commerce) 06.2020 - 09.2021 (1 year 4 months)

Implemented features:

- Creating new UI and migrate multi-page website on new UI.
- · Merging several multi-page website into one, structuring data and content.
- · Support Legacy projects.
- · Creating UI for a few multi-page website, from zero to result.

UI DEVELOPER (JS)

Digital Chain (Gambling) 01.2020 - 05.2020 (5 months)

Implemented features:

- Implementation automatization for creating promo landing page for sports events.
- · Creating landing page for special sport events.
- · Implementation automatization for creating Animated HTML Banners,
- following the specifications and requirements of the advertising platform.

EDUCATION

2015-2018

Kharkiv National University Of Radioelectronics Radiotechnics Engineering / Bachelor's degree

2011-2015

NKPT Technical College System Administrator